Good morning, this is Yuna Nakamura.
I'd like to introduce you to some fun and current trends!
I look forward to working with you!
Yuna Nakamura is a 16-year-old member of Shirisu Ebisu Chugaku!
Her hobby is fishing, and she is quite good at it!
Yuna will be introducing us to
Sweet and sour strawberry sweets!
Today, let's check out the sweets using strawberries that are in season now!
What's hot at the main store in Shinjuku Taka
It's a tart made with Benihoppe!
It uses a lot of benihoppe with just the right amount of sourness!
What's more, the sauce is made
The berry sauce is a combination of berry sauces with a strong sourness.
Inside is a tart filled with strawberry mousse and cream.
The cream has a slight aroma of strawberries.
The cream has a hint of strawberry flavor, and it goes well with the strawberries.
Thank you for watching!
You can only taste it now with butter.
Pancakes filled with strawberries in season!
The fluffy pancakes are made with fermented butter from Hokkaido, tofu and honey!
The rich pancakes are a perfect match for the tartness of the strawberries!
The pancakes are finished with a rich, sweet and sour strawberry sauce!
The crunchy coconut meringue accentuates the flavor.
When you try it, you'll see
The pancakes are fluffy and moist.
The moderately sweet whipped cream and rich custard go well with the sweet and sour strawberries.
Kihachi Cafe is currently holding a Spring Strawberry Fair!
Spring Strawberry Fair is now being held at Kihachi Cafe!
The popular Napoleon Pie and other limited-time-only menu items are now available, using strawberries in abundance!
We recommend the following
Rich strawberry jam and strawberry cream
Strawberry cream
Strawberry puree and other ingredients are combined with fresh cream to make Chantilly cream.
Strawberry slices and strawberry crunch
and strawberry crunch on top.
Finally, decorate with strawberries like a flower.
A gorgeous spring strawberry parfait is ready!
It is sweet, fresh and delicious!
It's so luxurious to be able to taste different kinds of strawberries!
It's a taste that can only be enjoyed during this season!
Good morning, my name is Yuna Nakamura.
Yes, today you are going to show us your special skill?
Yes, my special skill is hula hooping.
Today is the first time I'm going to try spinning two hula hoops at the same time.
Please do it.
I'll do it.
Two.
Yes, sir.
You're so good!
He even did a cartwheel!
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Thank you very much for showing off your skills.
And I look forward to working with you in the future.
Thank you very much!
That's all for now!
I'm Yuna Nakamura, student number 17 of Ebichu Junior High School, Ebisu Junior High School.
I look forward to working with you.
I'm 16 years old and a sophomore in high school.
I'm really nervous.
I tried spinning two hula hoops at the same time for the first time.
But when they went round, I thought I had failed.
I said "I failed" and started to scavenge.
I started to feel more confident.
When I turned the hoops...
I thought, "I can do it.
But I couldn't.
My father enjoys fishing.
I think I've been fishing since I was in early elementary school.
I haven't been able to go fishing much since I joined the shrimp club.
The last one I caught was the sea bream that was on the VTR.
I haven't been able to go there recently, so I'd like to go there soon.
There's a kind of sea bream called "Ito Nyorai".
Is that kind of sea bream caught from a boat? You catch it from a boat.
It's pretty easy.
It's easy even for beginners.
It's a gutsy way to fish, so I recommend it.
I want to go to Nagasaki
I want to go to Nagasaki and catch squid by egging.
I've never caught squid before.
I've been trying to find a way to catch squid, but I've never been able to catch it.
I've never actually caught any squid.
I'd like to go in spring and fall, when squid are often caught.
I am addicted to making sweets.
I make
I make simple cakes and cupcakes.
cupcakes, etc.
and decorating them.
Baking sweets is my hobby these days.
Cupcakes?
Steamed bread?
I'm into steamed buns and other microwaveable treats.
I'm into making sweets that can be made in a microwave.
I often look them up on Instagram and TikTok.
With a smile and a lot of energy
I'll do my best to provide you with lots of up-to-date information
I will do my best.
Thank you for watching.
Thank you for watching!